let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The associability of = operator is ________.",
    answer: "b.) Left to Right",
    options: [
      "a.) Right to Left",
      "b.) Left to Right",
      "c.) None of these",
      "d.) All of above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which operator has LOWEST priority?",
    answer: "d.) ()",
    options: [
      "a.) ++",
      "b.) %",
      "c.) ||",
      "d.) ()"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which operator has HIGHEST priority?",
    answer: "a.) ()",
    options: [
      "a.) ()",
      "b.) ||",
      "c.) %",
      "d.) ++"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Integer Division results in ___________.",
    answer: "a.) Truncating the fractional part",
    options: [
      "a.) Truncating the fractional part",
      "b.) Rounding the fractional part",
      "c.) Floating value",
      "d.) An error is generated"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The typecast operator is ____________.",
    answer: "b.) (data type)",
    options: [
      "a.) cast ()",
      "b.) (data type)",
      "c.) //",
      "d.) “ ”"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Explicit type conversion is known as ___________.",
    answer: "b.) Casting",
    options: [
      "a.) Separation",
      "b.) Casting",
      "c.) Conversion",
      "d.) Disjunction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "a+=4 means ____________.",
    answer: "a.) a=a+4",
    options: [
      "a.) a=a+4",
      "b.) a=4",
      "c.) a+4=a",
      "d.) a=4+4"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "p++ executes faster than p=p+1 because ______________________.",
    answer: "c.) p++ is a single instruction",
    options: [
      "a.) p uses registers",
      "b.) ++ is faster than +",
      "c.) p++ is a single instruction",
      "d.) All of above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which statement is correct?",
    answer: "a.) C Library functions provide I/O facilities",
    options: [
      "a.) C Library functions provide I/O facilities",
      "b.) C inherent I/O facilities",
      "c.) C doesn’t have I/O facilities",
      "d.) Both (a) and (c)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Header files in C contain ___________.",
    answer: "b.) Library functions",
    options: [
      "a.) Compiler Commands",
      "b.) Library functions",
      "c.) Header information of C Programs",
      "d.) Operators for files"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which pair is used for single character I/O.?",
    answer: "a.) getchar() and putchar()",
    options: [
      "a.) getchar() and putchar()",
      "b.) scanf() and printf()",
      "c.) input() and output()",
      "d.) None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "The printf() returns __________ value when an error occurs.",
    answer: "c.) Negative Value",
    options: [
      "a.) Positive value",
      "b.) Zero",
      "c.) Negative Value",
      "d.) None of these"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Identify wrong statement:",
    answer: "c.) putchar(“x”)",
    options: [
      "a.) putchar(65)",
      "b.) putchar(‘x’)",
      "c.) putchar(“x”)",
      "d.) putchar(‘\\n’)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "An Ampersand in scanf() before the name of a variable denotes ___________.",
    answer: "c.) Address",
    options: [
      "a.) Actual Value",
      "b.) Variable Name",
      "c.) Address",
      "d.) Data Type"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Symbolic constants can be defined using ____________.",
    answer: "a.) #define",
    options: [
      "a.) #define",
      "b.) const",
      "c.) symbols",
      "d.) None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Null character is represented by ____________.",
    answer: "b.) \\0",
    options: [
      "a.) \\n",
      "b.) \\0",
      "c.)\\o",
      "d.)\\e"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Which header file is essential for using strcmp() function.?",
    answer: "a.) string.h",
    options: [
      "a.) string.h",
      "b.) strings.h",
      "c.) text.h",
      "d.) strcmp.h"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "malloc() used in Dynamic Memory Allocation is available in ____________.",
    answer: "d.) stdio.h",
    options: [
      "a.) stream.h",
      "b.) malloc.h",
      "c.) alloc.h",
      "d.) stdio.h"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Testing & Conversion character functions in C are available in ____________.",
    answer: "a.) ctype.h",
    options: [
      "a.) ctype.h",
      "b.) string.h",
      "c.) math.h",
      "d.) conio.h"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "C supports ________ Looping statements.",
    answer: "b.) 3",
    options: [
      "a.) 5",
      "b.) 3",
      "c.) 6",
      "d.) 8"
    ]
  },
];